uefa.com 2015-12-18

# UEFA Privacy Policy - UEFA.com

**UEFA Privacy Policy**  
 **UEFA**  
 **Union des Associations Européennes de Football**  
 **Route de Genève 46**  
 **Case postale**  
 **CH-1260 Nyon 2**  
 **Switzerland**

UEFA takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully to learn more about UEFA's use of your personal identifying information that UEFA collect when you visit UEFA's official website at www.uefa.com (hereinafter referred to as: the "Website"). UEFA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. You are therefore responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy.

 **What this Privacy Policy covers**  
This Privacy Policy covers UEFA's treatment of personal identifying information that UEFA collects when you are on the Website and when you use services on the Website, as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also covers UEFA's treatment of any personal identifying information that UEFA's business partners share with UEFA unless otherwise stated.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any companies or legal entities that UEFA does not own or control or to any persons that UEFA does not employ or manage, including without limitation third-party advertisers or sponsors to whom you provide information. UEFA is not responsible for privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to link from the Website, and UEFA encourages you to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share information.

 **Information collection and use**  
UEFA does not collect personal identifying information when you access the Website homepage and browse the Website without disclosing your personal data except as described in this Privacy Policy or the relevant part of the Website and except cookies (see below under "cookies").

UEFA collects personal identifying information when you register on the Website, when you use certain products or services on the Website and when you enter promotions, sweepstakes or similar services sponsored by UEFA or its business partners. UEFA may also receive personal identifying information from its business partners.

When you register, UEFA asks for your name, email address, and some other personal information. Once you register with UEFA and/or sign in to our products or services, you are not anonymous to UEFA.

In case you signing in via your Facebook authentication services (Facebook account), UEFA may receive some information from Facebook, but you remain solely responsible for your whole relationship with Facebook, including, without limitation, any content on the Facebook website.

In case you terminate your membership with Facebook and/or terminate the links between Facebook and our Website, UEFA will delete all data received from Facebook concerning you if you ask UEFA to do so. You can do so using the same easy way as for the ability to access your personal identifying information as defined in this Policy. Further, Facebook may require UEFA to delete data received from Facebook API in case of violation of their terms.

If Facebook will disable any links to our website, UEFA will delete all your date received through the use of the Facebook API, unless it is a basic account information or UEFA have received explicit consent from you to retain your data.

UEFA also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your Internet Protocol address (IP address), which identifies your computer, UEFA's cookies information and the page you requested.

UEFA uses information collected for three general purposes: for technical administration of the Website, for research and development to achieve and maintain a high service level and for customer information (to customise the content you see, to fulfil your request for certain products and services and to contact you about specials and new products and services).

 **Information sharing and disclosure**  
UEFA will not sell or rent your personal identifying information without your consent. UEFA may send personal identifying information about you to third parties when:

• UEFA has your consent to share the information;  
• UEFA needs to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;  
• UEFA needs to send the information to third parties who work on behalf of UEFA to provide a product or service to you (unless otherwise stated so, these third parties do not have any rights to use the personal identifying information UEFA provides to them beyond what is necessary to provide a product or service to you);  
• UEFA responds to courts or authorities;  
• UEFA finds that your actions on the Website violate UEFA Website Terms and Conditions of Use or any other UEFA's guidelines or rules applicable for specific services; or  
• UEFA finds that it is necessary, as determined in UEFA’s sole discretion, to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, emergency situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any persons, violations to UEFA’s terms of use or as otherwise required by law.

 **Cookies**  
UEFA may set and access UEFA's cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive.

UEFA uses its own cookies for number of purposes, mainly to:  
• access your information when you "sign in", so that we can provide you with customized content;  
• keep track of preferences you specify while you are using UEFA services;  
• estimate and report our total audience size and traffic;  
• conduct research and development to improve the Website contents and services and achieve and maintain a high service level.

UEFA may allow third parties that are presenting promotions or researching users response to advertisement on some of our pages to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Third parties' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not this one.

 **Children's privacy**  
The Website and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13.

If you are not yet legally an adult (Under 18) but are 13 or older, please use this website only after obtaining permission from your parent or legal guardian.

The protection of personal data of children and adolescents is of particular concern to UEFA, UEFA recommends that parents discuss the user of the Internet and the provision of information on websites with their children before allowing minors between 13 and 18 to register.

UEFA will not knowingly collect personal data about visitors under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. In the event that UEFA learns having collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, that information will be deleted as quickly as possible and the access as a User immediately denied.

If you believe that UEFA might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at dataprotection@uefa.com.

 **Access to your personal identifying information**  
UEFA gives you the ability to access your personal identifying information by sending us an email including in the title of the email the reference to personal identifying information at dataprotection@uefa.com.

UEFA allows you to challenge the data that it holds about you and you may have such data rectified, amended or completed.

 **Security**  
If you communicate with UEFA by email, you should note that the secrecy of Internet email is uncertain. By sending sensitive or confidential email messages or information which are not encrypted you accept the risk of such uncertainty and possible lack of confidentiality over the Internet. In certain areas, UEFA uses industry standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

Generally, UEFA takes precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

 **Changes in this Privacy Policy**  
This policy may be amended from time to time. If we amend the Privacy Policy in any way we will place an updated version on this page of the Website. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website.

 **Updating your information**  
You may review, correct, update or change your personal information at any time by accessing your account on uefa.com.

 **Privacy compliance**  
UEFA is subject to Swiss data protection laws when collecting and processing personal identifying information.

 **Questions or suggestions**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please send an email to dataprotection@uefa.com.

©UEFA.com 1998-2012. All rights reserved.

©UEFA.com 1998-2015. All rights reserved.
